Finding aid for WUOM Records, 1914-1982
Bentley Historical Library
- Audio Material, 1930s-1970s
  - Sound Reels (7-inch)
    - WUOM: Original Productions
      - "Special of the Week" [speech/panel discussion]
        (broadcast November 1961-[August] 1973. 2 reels retained. Most programs originated in Washington, D.C. and were distributed by the National Association for Educational Broadcasting network.)
        - "Special of the Week" Speech commemorating the fifth anniversary of the Peace Corps / Jack Hood Vaughn ([R93A]), 1966 March 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-14-1-1]; (New director of the Peace Corps making his first address in Ann Arbor upon 5th anniversary of the Peace Corps.)
        - "Special of the Week" Black Nationalism / Reverend Albert Cleague ([R94A]), 1967 October 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-14-2-1]; (Rev. Albert Cleague, black militant leader, speaking on Black Nationalism in Session of America in Crisis Teach-In at the University of Michigan.)
    - U-M Ceremonies and Convocations
      University of Michigan: Ceremonies and Convocations. Recordings of various ceremonial events, including building dedications. In general, though WUOM regularly broadcasts the university commencement exercises, these recordings, along with recordings of Honors Convocation, are kept only when transcripts of the addresses are not yet available.
      - Birthday Dinner Ceremonies Honoring Alexander Grant Ruthven / Ruthven; Harlan H. Hatcher; Frank [Whitman?], master of ceremonies ([R95A]), 1962 June 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-15-1-1]; (Recording of Birthday Dinner for Alexander Ruthven, Hatcher, Frank [Whitman?] as the master of ceremonies. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Commencement 1961: Address by Edward R. Murrow (Who Speaks for America?) ([R96A -R79A]), 1961 June 17; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-16-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Broadcast of 1961 Commencement Exercises. Edward R. Murrow, Director of the U.S. Information Agency gives the 1961 commencement address at the Michigan Stadium. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
        - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-16-1-1-2]; (Tape 2 of 2; Broadcast of 1961 Commencement Exercises. Edward R. Murrow, Director of the U.S. Information Agency gives the 1961 commencement address at the Michigan Stadium. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Commencement 1963: Address by C.P. Snow. ([R98A]), 1963 June 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-17-1-1]; (Broadcast of 1963 Commencement exercises. Address given by Sir Charles P. Snow. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Chrysler Center ([R99A]), 1967 November 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-18-1-1]; (Recording of the dedication ceremony for the Chrysler Center. Speakers include Harlan Hatcher; Lynn Townsend; Chairman of the Board of Directors. Chrysler; Harry Chesbrough, VP, Chrysler; Gordon Van Nylen, Dean, Engineering College. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Federal Mogul Building ([R100A]), 1963 February 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-19-1-1]; (Recording of the dedication ceremony of the Federal Mogul building, Harlan Hatcher and George Romney and others speaking. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Kresge Hearing Research Institute ([R101A]), 1963 May 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-20-1-1]; (Recording of the dedication ceremony of the Kresge Hearing Research Institute, Harlan Hatcher, William N. Hubbard, H. Vaughn Whitehead and others speaking. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Law School Television ([R102A]), 1961 January 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-21-1-1]; (Recording of the dedication ceremony of the Law School Television, Allan Smith,John Satterfield, Harlan Hatcher, William N. Hubbard, H. Vaughn Whitehead speaking. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Matthaei Botanical Gardens ([R103A]), 1962 June 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-22-1-1]; (Recording of the dedication ceremony of the Matthaei Botanical Gardens, Harlan Hatcher, Frederick C. Matthaei, William C. Steere, G. Geoffrey Norman speaking. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: Towsley Center for Continuing Medical Education([R104A-R105A]), [1969 March 27]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 19)
        - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-23-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Recording of the dedication ceremony of the Towsley Center for Continuing Medical Education, Robben W. Fleming, Harry A. Towsley and others speaking. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
        - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-23-1-1-2]; (Tape 2 of 2; Recording of the dedication ceremony of the Towsley Center for Continuing Medical Education, Robben W. Fleming, Harry A. Towsley and others speaking. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
      - Dedication Ceremony: University Events Building [Crisler Arena] ([R106A]), 1968 February 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-24-1-1]; (Recording of the dedication ceremony of the University Events Building (Crisler Arena), Bill Fleming; Donald F. Tucker; Marcus Plant; Bob Brown; Fritz Crisler; Robben W. Fleming. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.) (Box 20)
      - Special Student Convocation: Participation and Responsibility / Harlan H. Hatcher ([R107A-R108A]), 1965 March 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
        - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-25-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Harlan H. Hatcher addresses student activism. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
        - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-25-1-1-2]; (Tape 2 of 2; Harlan H. Hatcher addresses student activism. Part of WUOM's recordings on UM Ceremonies & Convocations.)
    - U-M Conferences and Lectures
      - Alumni University
        - "Today's Graduate Student" / Stephen H. Spurr, recorded April 29, 1965 broadcast Lecture Hour, August 19, 1965, [R109A] (Box 20)
      - Creative Arts Festival
        - Poetry Reading: W.D. Snodgrass; introduction by Donald Hall ([R110A]), 1963 March 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-26-1-1]; (Broadcast July 11 1963, Part of the Creative Arts Festival. Reading of a selection of poems by W.D. Snodgrass, "The Lovers Go Fly A Kite," "Lobsters in the Window", "No Use" "Heart's Needle No. 9", "Point Pelee in March", "San Francisco at Night" (translation), "Monet: "Les Nymphéas", "The Men's Room in the College Chapel", "April Inventory", "Poem about a Moth", "The Knee", "The Pike", "The Wallpaper Flower", "Pundstrom", "The Spheres", "To A Nightingale." Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
        - Poetry Reading: James Dickey; introduction by Donald Hall, (broadcast Lecture Hour) ([R111A]), 1963 May 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-27-1-1]; (Recorded May 13, 1963, Broadcast June 26, 1963, James Dickey reads "At Darien Bridge", "Cherrylog Road", "Hunting Civil War Relics in Nimblewell Creek", "The Being", "The Lifeguard", "A Folksinger of the Thirties", "The Performance", "The Hospital Window", "In the Marble Quarry", "Heaven of Animals". Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
        - Poetry Reading: John Berryman ([R112A-R113A]), 1965 March 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-28-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Recording of a poetry reading by John Berryman at the Creative Arts Festival, 1965. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-28-1-1-2]; (Tape 2 of 2; Recording of a poetry reading by John Berryman at the Creative Arts Festival, 1965. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
        - Poetry Reading: Radcliffe Squires broadcast Lecture Hour ([R114A]), 1965 March 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-29-1-1]; (At Creative Arts Festival, recorded March 25, 1965, Broadcast September 16, 1965 reads "The Ancient One", "Prince Edward Island", "The Subway Bridge Charles Station to Kendall", "Two Children", "In Memoriam, Ernest Hemingway", unknown poem, "The Agora", "Hermodactylus", "The Cafe in Salonica", "A Letter from Crete to Delphi", "The Statues in Athens", "Thassos", "Nestor's Palace", "Returning to Milan", "The Beginning", "Mountains like Slate." Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
        - Poetry Reading: Galway Kinnell, broadcast Lecture Hour ([R115A]), 1961 April 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-30-1-1]; (Recorded April 12, 1961, Broadcast May 22, 1961, reads "Easter", "Poor Dogs", "The Correspondence School Instructor Says Farewell", "To A Child in Calcutta", "Ceiling Fan", "The River is East", "The Homecoming of Emma Lazarus", "Flowering Herding Pictures on Mount Monadnock" ," Includes paper insert for announcers. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
      - College of Literature, Science, and the Arts
        - Afro-American: A Survey History [pilot course, Afro-American Studies Program] / Harold Cruse, et al., broadcast, Fall 1969; 12 reels (Box 20)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Cruse and Born ([R116A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-1-1]; (Tape 1; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #1 and #2: course introduction and philosophy. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 1; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #1 and #2. On African History, Pre-Colombian Africa and Anthropology, and the Early Slave Trade. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Smedley and Lawrence (R117A), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-2-1]; (Tape 2; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #3 and #4. On the evolution of humanity in Africa and early Anthropological research on humanity's origin. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-2-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #3 and #4. On the contributions of African culture to the New World. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Smedley and Hall (R118A), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-3-1]; (Tape 3; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #5 and #6. The continuation of Smedley's lecture in Post-Neolithic period of Africa, migration out of Africa, Mali Empire. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-3-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 3; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #5 and #6. Discussion of discourse in African-American Studies and African-Americans scholarship and history of Slavery in the New World. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Hall and Freehling ([R119A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-4-1]; (Tape 4; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #7 and #8. On Slavery and Religious Education in Latin America. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-4-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 4; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #7 and #8. On family and social structure in African-American families. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Freehling and Toll ([R120A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-5-1]; (Tape 5; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #9 and #10. The effects of slave resistance and plantation slavery. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-5-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 5; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #9 and #10. Changes in African-American culture and life after the Civil War until World War I. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Toll and Cruse ([R121A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-6-1]; (Tape 6; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #11 and #12. Black participation in the Civil War and Reconstruction Politics in Southern States. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-6-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 6; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #11 and #12. Causes and origins of the Civil War, Reconstruction and Industrialization. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Cruse and Toll ([R122A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-7-1]; (Tape 7; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #13 and #14. On the results of the Reconstruction Era. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-7-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 7; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #13 and #14. Reconstruction and its Aftermath, industrialization and economic stagnation. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Toll and Waters ([R123A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-8-1]; (Tape 8; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #15 and #16. Reconstruction era economic development in the South until 1900. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-8-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 8; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #15 and #16. Backlash to Reconstruction and the beginnings of the Great Migration. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Cruse and Waters ([R124A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-9-1]; (Tape 9; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #17 and #18. Post-Reconstruction (1890s) Black American Leadership, Intellectualism, and Arts: Frederick Douglass, W. E. B. Du Bois, Booker T. Washington. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-9-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 9; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #17 and #18. Introduction on course philosophy, historiography; lecture is on the development of Black Labor Movement. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Cruse ([R125A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-10-1]; (Tape 10; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #19 and #20. Post-Reconstruction (1890s) Development of Black education; White Industrial Contributions to Black Education, Booker T. Washington and Industrial Education, DuBois and Washington divide. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-10-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 10; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #19 and #20. African American Education, The rise of Booker T. Washington, the DuBois' Niagara Movement. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Berry and Cruse ([R126A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-11-1]; (Tape 11; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #21 and #22. Problems and events that lead to the founding of the NAACP. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-11-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 11; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #21 and #22.Post-World War I, Marcus Garvey, The Great Migration, A. Philip Randolph, Black Radicalism of the 1920s and 30s. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - College of LSA: Afro-American: A Survey History; Wright and Cruse ([R127A]), 1969 Fall; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
            - [Part 1], [8738-SR-31-12-1]; (Tape 12; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #23 and #24. Stokeley Carmichael, integration, assimilation in America. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
            - [Part 2], [8738-SR-31-12-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 12; Recording of the pilot course of the Afro-American Studies Program, #23 and #24. Final course papers, examination, course wrap-up. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
      - Student Legal Defense Committee
        - Reclassification Rally: "Dissent and Draft" / Irene Murphy; Ross Wilhelm; Philip Hart ([R128A]), 1966 April 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-32-1-1]; (Panel discussion by the Student Legal Defense Committee. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
      - Unidentified Sponsorship
        - Poetry reading: Donald Hall ([R129A]), [Undated]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-33-1-1]; (Donald Hall reads "Munch's Scream", "Christmas Eve in Whitneyville, 1955", "Cinders." Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
        - Press conference with Robert Frost ([R130A]), 1962 April 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-34-1-1]; (Recording of Robert Frost answering questions at a press conference. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
      - Vietnam "Action" Teach-In
        - Vietnam "Action" Teach-In: Speeches and panel discussion ([R133A-R135A]), 1969 September 20; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-35-1-1-1]; (Tape 1; Recording of speeches and ralley at the Vietnam "Action" Teach-In. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures. Panelists include: Robert Sklar, Howard Zinn, Andrew Pulley, Dave Dellinger.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-35-1-1-2]; (Tape 2; Recording of speeches and ralley at the Vietnam "Action" Teach-In. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures. Panelists include: Robert Sklar, Howard Zinn, Andrew Pulley, Dave Dellinger.)
          - [Reel 3, Part 1], [8738-SR-35-1-1-3]; (Tape 3; Recording of speeches and ralley at the Vietnam "Action" Teach-In. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures. Panelists include: Robert Sklar, Howard Zinn, Andrew Pulley, Dave Dellinger.)
      - War Moratorium (sponsor: New Mobilization to End the War)
        - War Moratorium: "Business and the War" ([R136A=r137A]), 1969 October 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-36-1-1-1]; (Panelists are: Robben W. Fleming; Mike Ryder; J.B. Ritchie; Stan McGlaughlin.War Moratorium panel discussion moderated by John Nanis; Flemming talks on "The Effect of the Vietnam War on the University", Mike Ryder on business and Vietnam, Stan McGlaughlin concludes on perceptions of Vietnam and military affairs, question and answer session. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-36-1-1-2]; (Panelists are: Robben W. Fleming; Mike Ryder; J.B. Ritchie; Stan McGlaughlin. War Moratorium panel discussion moderated by John Nanis, Stan McGlaughlin concludes on perceptions of Vietnam and military affairs. Part of WUOM's recordings on University Conferences and Lectures.)
    - U-M History
      The University of Michigan: History subseries is composed chiefly of recordings of oral history interviews with university faculty and staff.
      - Erich Walter Talks about Harlan Hatcher ([R138A]), 1961 December 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-37-1-1]; (Recording of an interview of Erich Walter by Jack Hamiliton on Harlan Hatcher.)
      - Interview with T. Hawley Tapping ([R139A]), 1958; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 20)
        - [Part 1], [8738-SR-38-1-1]; (T. Hawley Tapping discussing the history of U of M Alumni organizations.)
    - U-M Sesquicentennial Celebration
      - $55 Million Dollar Campaign
        - $55 Million Dollar Campaign Radio spots / Harlan H. Hatcher ([R140A]), 1967 February 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-39-1-1-1]; (A series of radio spots first segment begins at 0:48, second segment begins at 2:13; on fundraising and capital at the University during the sesquicentennial.)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-39-1-1-2]; (Tape content does not match original description; content is not Harlan Hatcher, unknown speakers talking about medicine.)
      - University of Michigan Birthday Symposium [Alumni Weekend]
        - "The Right of Free Expression" / Arthur Miller; Fred Hindley, host ([R141A]), 1967 March 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-40-1-1]; (This tape follows Wallace - Gingrich tape of the same subject. Includes question-answer session, Broadcast Special of the Week/ UM Birthday Symposium Alumni Weekend.)
      - Voices of Civilization Lecture Series, October 2-6, 1967 (Major Ceremony IV)
        - "Race Relations" / Ralph Ellison broadcast Special of the Week ([R142A]), 1967 October 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-41-1-1]; (NER (National Educational Radio) Special of the Week; Ralph Ellison on race relations. Voices of Civilization Lecture Series, October 2-6, 1967.)
        - "The Shift of Power from East to West" / Dean Acheson, ([R143A-R145A]), 1967 October 02; 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7-1/2 ips (Box 21)